대체 이게 뭐야!
What the hell is that?!
무슨 소리니?
네가 그랬어?
What the hell is that?
Is that you?
- 너 아침잠이 많구나
- 건드리지 마!
-You're really not a morning person.
-Just back off!
Get up! Get up! Get up!
빨랑 일어나!
빨랑! 빨랑!
What is that noise?
이게 누구 소리야
You!
너!
It's the chick.
우리 병아리가 요즘
변하고 있어
She's going through some changes.
What kind of changes?
변하다니
수의사 말로는
수탉이 돼 가는 거래
The vet seems to think...
...she's becoming a rooster.
We're getting a second opinion.
다른 수의사를 만나보려고
The One With the Embryos
- 어서 와
- 아침 8시부터 쇼핑이야?
Why are you shopping
at 8 in the morning?
I've been up since 6...
망할 수탉 때문에
6시부터 깼거든
...thanks to somebody's
dumb-ass rooster.
You should get rid of those animals.
They shouldn't be in an apartment.
제발 어떻게 좀 해라
아파트에서 키우면 안돼
특히 식칼과 요리책이
난무하는 환경에선
Especially not with these
knives and cookbooks around.
I'm going to the doctor
and see if I'm ready...
난 병원에 가야겠어
수정란을 자궁에 넣을
준비가 됐나 봐야지
...to have Frank and Alice's embryo
transferred into my uterus.
How will they know?
그걸 어떻게 아는데?
They'll just see if my
endometrial layer is thick.
자궁내벽의 두께를
검사하는 거야
I can check that for you.
그건 나도 봐줄 수 있어
Okay, think "thick."
- 두껍길 빌어줘
- 행운을 빈다
Good luck!
- 얘들아, 행운을 빌어줘
- 행운을 빈다
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
잘될 거야
어쨌든 내가 맞지?
-I'm still right.
-That is so not true.
- 웃기지 마
- 뭐가?
What?
I know it's her laundry day...
세탁하는 날이라 아줌마 팬티
입었을 거라고 했더니 저래
...and that means she's wearing
her old-lady underpants.
I can check that for you.
내가 확인해줄 수 있는데
You two think you know
me and Rachel...
우리가 너희를 아는 것보다
너희가 우릴 더 잘 알까?
...better than we know you.
Well, we do.
네, 물론이에요
You can only eat Tic Tacs
in even numbers.
구강세정제도 짝을
맞춰 먹지?
What's that about?
무슨 사연인데
And you!
Ross, if you check Rachel's bag...
그리고 너... 로스?
쇼핑백에 반만 남은
과자상자가 있을 거야
...you'll find a half-eaten box
of cookies in there.
You're good.
예리한데?
These are not.
맛은 꽝이다
I'm so not impressed.
Everybody snacks when they shop.
그게 뭐, 쇼핑할 땐
누구나 군것질해
- 맞아
- 그래?
Ross, how many items
left in that bag?
로스, 거기 몇 가지
물건이 들어있지?
Five.
다섯 가지
그거 다 맞히는 데
10달러 걸겠어
Okay, 10 bucks says we can
name every item in that bag.
-How many guesses?
-Six.
몇 번 시도해서?
여섯 번
Challenge extended.
도전 신청입니다
-Deal!
-Challenge accepted.
좋아!
도전 수락입니다
All right, we'll start with...
좋았어, 그럼 우선...
...apples.
사과
사과로 시작됐습니다
We'll be starting with apples.
당장 집어치워
Stop that now.
Yes.
있군요
Okay. Tortilla chips.
좋아, 토르티야 칩
요구르트
-Yogurt.
-Diet soda.
다이어트 소다
네, 그래요, 맞아요
-Orange juice.
-There's no orange juice! We win!
오렌지 주스
아니! 그건 없어!
이겼다!
한 번 더 남았어
They have another guess.
Well, we won that one.
거긴 이겼잖아
Okay. The last thing is
- 좋아, 마지막 하나는...
- 워워워! 워! 워워!
아니, 그건 2주 남았어
Not for another two weeks.
I got it.
알았다, 스카치... 테이프!
Scotch...
...tape.
이건 어떻게 알아냈지?
How did you know
she would buy Scotch tape?
간밤에 괴물놀이 하느라
우리가 다 써버렸거든
We used up theirs last night
making scary faces.
Oh, man!
참 내!
좋아, 10달러!
내놔! 토해내! 지불하시지!
All right! Ten bucks.
Fork it over.
Cough it up. Pay the piper.
Give me it!
냉큼!
You don't know us better.
I want a rematch.
이걸로는 증명이 안돼
다시 해
And no stupid grocery questions.
Real, personal questions.
이런 잡동사니 말고
진짜 개인적인 문제로
And the winner gets $100.
그래, 이긴 쪽에 100달러
-Serious?
-Are you scared?
지, 진짜?
떨리세요?
No.
전혀...
Who makes up the questions?
문제는 누가 내지?
Ross will do it.
오빠가 낼 거야
어럽쇼? 오빠가 낼 거야?
Sure, Ross will do it.
It's not like he has a job
or a child or a life of his own.
내가 그렇게 한가한
인간처럼 보이나?
-Fine. We'll ask Phoebe.
-No, I want to play.
그럼 피비한테 부탁하자
아냐, 나 하고 싶어
Looks like your uterus
is ready for implantation.
준비가 된 듯하군요
I knew it!
I felt really thick this morning.
그럴 줄 알았어, 아침에
두툼한 느낌이 들더라구
Okay, so what's now?
Go get the eggs. Put them in there.
그럼 어서 수정란
갖다가 집어넣어요
It'll take a little while
to prepare the embryos.
수정란들을 준비하려면
시간이 좀 걸릴 거예요
-Embryos? As in more than one?
-Five, actually.
수정란들?
하나가 아닌가요?
정확히 다섯 개예요
Where am I giving birth...
다섯 개? 암탉처럼 계단 밑
상자 속에 낳으라는 건가요?
...in a hospital or
a big box under the stairs?
Doing five gives you a 25% chance
that at least one will attach.
성공률 25%를
감안한 거랍니다
겨우 25%? 실패할 확률이
75%나 된다는 말인가요?
That's it? 25%?
That means that it's, like,
75% chance of no baby at all?
그럼 아예 2백 개쯤 넣으면
확률이 높아질 텐데
I was thinking,
what are the odds...
...if you stuff 200 of them in there?
Sweetie, now...
자기 누님은 여자지
풍선껌자판기가 아냐
...she's a woman,
not a gumball machine.
제대로 될 때까지 몇 번이고
해줄 테니까 걱정하지 마
Don't worry. I'll do this as many
times as it takes to get it right.
하지만 기회는 한 번 뿐이야
The thing is, we kind of
only have one shot.
It costs $16,000 each time you do this.
한 번 시술하는 데
1만 6천 달러거든요
Sixteen thousand dollars?!
1만 6천 달러?
Well, it's 20 in California.
캘리포니아에선
2만 달러인데요...
이번에 우리 재산을
몽땅 털어 넣었어요
We're kind of using all the money
we have to do it this one time.
와우!
내 자궁에 너무 부담을 주는데?
Okay, that's a lot of
pressure on me and my uterus.
확실한 임신을 위해 내가
할 수 있는 일은 없나요?
Maybe there's something I can do
to make sure I get pregnant.
안 됐지만 없어요
No, I'm sorry.
Wow, you guys really
don't know anything.
제대로 하는 게 뭐죠?
Why don't you get drunk? It worked
for a bunch of girls in my high school.
술을 마셔봐, 고등학교 땐
그럼 임신이 잘 되던데
-So how's the test coming?
-Hey, you're touching the game board.
- 잘돼 가?
- 야, 만지지 마
Sorry.
미안...
You freak.
하여간 별종이야
얘들아
Do you realize that
any minute now...
지금쯤 피비가 아기를
가졌을지도 몰라
...Phoebe could be pregnant?
I know, I know.
그러게
정말 엄청난 사건이야
It's such a huge,
life-altering thing.
- 그래
- 맞아
- 준비 끝났어
- 정말? 좋았어!
The test is ready.
Okay. Each team will
answer 10 questions.
좋아요
팀 당 열 문제인데
The first team to answer
the most questions wins.
먼저 많은 문제를
맞힌 팀이 승리합니다
카테고리는
'공포와 혐오'
The categories are
"Fears and Pet Peeves"...
'고대사'
..."Ancient History"...
..."Literature"...
'문학'
...and "It's all Relative."
'가문의 비화'입니다
Now...
이제...
...the coin toss,
to see who goes first.
동전을 던져서 결정하겠습니다
Okay.
- 좋아요, 이번엔 콜을 하세요
- 그래!
Somebody call it this time.
Tails!
뒷면!
It's heads.
- 앞면입니다
- 으라차!
Gentlemen, pick your category.
남성 팀, 선택하시죠
"Fears and Pet Peeves."
'공포와 혐오'
"What is Monica's biggest pet peeve?"
모니카가 제일 싫어하는 건?
-Animals dressed as humans.
-Correct.
- 사람처럼 옷 입은 동물
- 정답!
-Ladies?
-Same category.
여성 팀?
같은 카테고리
"According to Chandler, what phenomenon
scares the bejesus out of him?"
챈들러가 세상에서 가장
끔찍하다고 느끼는 인물은?
Michael Flatley, Lord of the Dance!
댄스황제, 마이클 플랫리!
That is correct.
정답입니다!
The lrish jig guy?
그 아일랜드 지그 댄서?
His legs flail about
as if independent from his body!
몸이랑 다리가 따로 논다니깐!
Gentlemen, your pick.
남성 팀 차례입니다
"It's all Relative."
'가문의 비화'
"Monica and I had
a grandmother who died.
모니카의 할머니는 돌아가셨습니다
You both went to her funeral.
두 분 다 장례식에 가셨죠?
Name that grandmother."
할머님의 성함은?
-Nana?
-She has a real name.
함무니?
본명이 아냐
Althea!
- 알시아!
- 알시아! 확실해?
-What?
-I took a shot!
- 찍었어!
- 할머님을 찍었어?
With Althea?
- 알시아, 맞습니다
- 잘 찍었다!
-Althea is correct.
-Nice shooting!
"Literature."
'문학' 주세요!
"Every week the TV Guide comes
to Chandler and Joey's apartment.
챈들러와 조이의 아파트에는
매주 TV가이드가 배달됩니다
What name appears
on the address label?"
수취인은 누구로 돼있을까요?
Chandler gets it!
It's Chandler Bing!
챈들러가 봐! 챈들러 빙!
아냐!
안타깝지만 TV가이드는
'채낸들러 봉' 앞으로 옵니다
I'm afraid the TV Guide
comes to "Chanandler Bong."
I knew that!
난 알고 있었어!
레이첼, 머리 좀 써라!
Rachel, use your head!
Actually, it's Ms. Chanandler Bong.
정확히 '미스 채낸들러 봉'이지
Hello, teeny embryos.
안녕, 꼬마 수정란들아
I'm Phoebe Buffay. Hi!
피비 부페이란다, 반가워
I'm hoping to be your uterus
for the next nine months.
앞으로 아홉 달 동안
너희들 자궁이 될 거야
We're doing this
for Frank and Alice...
프랭크와 앨리스를 위해서야
거기서 나왔으니 너희도 알지?
...who you know.
You've been there.
They want you so much.
두 사람은 지금 절박하니까
들어가면 악착같이 매달려라
So when you guys get in there,
really grab on.
And I promise that I'll keep you
safe and warm...
집에 갈 때까지 내가
안전하게 보살펴줄게
...until you're ready
to have them take you home.
그럼...
Next time you see me,
if I'm screaming, don't worry.
나중에 만날 때 내가 비명을
지르더라고 염려할 건 없어
That's what's supposed to happen.
Ready?
- 준비됐어요?
- 네
Good luck!
잘해라
The score is nine to eight
in favor of the guys.
좋아요, 현재 9대 8로
남성 팀이 우세하니까
Ladies, if you miss this,
the game is theirs. Pick a category.
여성 팀이 이 문제를
놓치면 지게 됩니다
- 문제를 고르세요
- 가문의 비화!
"It's all Relative"!
-You don't have to shout everything.
-I'm sorry!
- 고함칠 필요 없어요
- 죄송합니다!
"What is the name
of Chandler's father's...
챈들러 아버지의 라스베가스
남성전용 스트립쇼 타이틀은?
...Las Vegas all-male burlesque?"
Viva Las Gaygas!
비바 라스'게이'가스!
Unfortunately, that is correct.
비통하게도 정답이다
야호!
All right. We have a tie.
그럼 동점이군요, 다행히
이럴 경우를 대비해뒀지
Luckily, I've prepared
for such an event.
The lightning round!
번개라운드!
30초 안에 가능한 한
많은 문제를 맞혀주세요
Thirty seconds.
All the questions you can answer.
너흰 죽었다, 번개라운드는
내가 꽉 잡고 있어!
You guys are dead!
I am so good at lightning rounds!
I majored in lightning rounds,
all right?
난 번개라운드 전공이야
끝장난 건 너희들이지
We'll destroy you.
내기할래?
Want to bet?
I'm so confused as to what
we've been doing so far.
여태까지 한 건 뭐였더라?
How about we play for more money?
Say 150?
더 걸어보자
150달러 어때?
One hundred and fifty dollars.
150달러 나왔습니다
Say 200?
200달러는 어떤가
200달러 나왔습니다
Two hundred dollars!
You're doing it again.
또 시작이야?
Excuse me.
실례할게
-I don't want to lose $200.
-We won't.
- 난 200달러 잃기 싫어
- 안 잃어!
- 알았어
- 300달러?
Three hundred?
- 모니카!
- 내기의 맛을 더하려는 거야
I'm spicing it up!
그럼 양념을 뿌려
내 돈 쓰지 말고
So play for some pepper!
Stop spending my money.
I got it!
좋았어, 우리가 이기면
그 수탉을 없애는 거야
If we win, they have to
get rid of the rooster.
우! 그거 절묘하다
That's interesting!
안돼, 우린 한 식구야
-No way! That rooster's family.
-The duck too!
오리도 같이!
The duck doesn't make noise!
오리는 조용한데 왜 이래!
병아리 성질을 건드리잖아
He gets the other one all riled up!
-We are not
-All right, hold on!
- 우린 절대...
- 잠깐!
If you win...
너희가 이기면 녀석을 포기할게
...we give up the bird.
But if we win...
대신 우리가 이기면
이 아파트를 넘겨
...we get your apartment.
-Deal!
-What?
- 좋아!
- 이런... 뭐?
미친 짓이야, 왜 우리가
아파트까지 걸어야 돼?
That's crazy. There's no way
we are betting the apartment.
All right, I'm in. Because either
he goes, or I'm buying a coyote.
좋았어, 저 녀석이 나가든지
내가 코요테를 키우든지
모니카, 아파트를 걸면
어떡하자는 거야
Betting the apartment?
I don't know about this.
레이첼, 난 한 문제도
안 틀렸어, 우리가 이겨
I have not missed one question
the whole game. I own this game!
-Look at my hand.
-You have the answers written there?
내 손을 봐
왜? 답이 적혔어?
No. Steady as a rock.
Now, are you with me?
전혀 안 떨리잖아
같이 할 거지?
All right, let's do it!
해보자!
- 힘내!
- 좋아
All right.
Gentlemen, you're up first.
남성 팀부터 갑니다
- 그래
- 좋아
You have 30 seconds.
시간은 30초
The lightning round begins
이제 번개라운드... 그만해
Stop it!
"Monica's nickname
when she was a hockey goalie?"
시작! 필드하키 골키퍼 시절
모니카의 별명은?
- 오방떡 수문장!
- 맞았어요!
-Big Fat Goalie.
-Correct!
"Rachel claims
it's her favorite movie."
레이첼이 제일 좋아한다고
우기는 영화는?
Dangerous Liaisons.
- '위험한 관계'
- 맞아!
하지만 실제로 좋아하는 건?
-"Her actual favorite is...?"
-Weekend at Bernie's.
- '공포의 주말'
- 정답!
"In what part of her body did Monica
get a pencil stuck at age 14?"
모니카가 14살 때
연필을 꽂았던 신체 부위는?
No!
으휴, 아냐!
귀야!
Her ear!
그렇다면 모니카는 수건을
몇 가지로 분류할까요?
"Monica categorizes her towels.
How many categories are there?"
-Everyday use.
-Fancy.
- 일상용
- 장식용
-Guest.
-Fancy guest.
- 접대용
- 특수접대용
-Two seconds.
-Eleven?
- 남은 시간 2초
- 어... 11가지?
Unbelievable!
Eleven is correct!
11가지, 이럴 수가!
정확합니다
아자!
All right.
좋아요, 남성 팀은 네 문제
여성 팀 나오세요
That's four for the guys.
Ladies, you're up!
- 좋아, 가자!
- 그래!
Thirty seconds on the clock.
역시 시간은 30초이며
다섯 문제를 맞히면 승리
Five correct questions
wins the game.
The lightning round begins now.
"Joey's favorite food?"
번개라운드 시작
조이가 제일 좋아하는 음식?
- 샌드위치
- 정답
-Sandwiches!
-Correct.
챈들러는 몇 살 때
여자 가슴을 처음 만졌나
"Chandler was how old when he
first touched a girl's breast?"
-14?
-No, 19.
- 14살?
- 아니, 19살
고맙다
Thanks, man.
"Joey had an imaginary
childhood friend.
조이가 어릴 적에
상상으로 만든 친구는?
-His name was...?"
-Maurice!
- 모리스!
- 정답! 직업은?
-"His profession was...?"
-Space cowboy!
- 우주 카우보이!
- 정답!
챈들러 빙의 직업은?
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
이런...
It has something to do with numbers!
맙소사, 숫자랑
관계 있는 건데...
-And processing!
-He carries a briefcase.
- 그리고 자료처리!
- 서류가방도 들고 다녀
이제 10초 남았습니다
Ten seconds.
You need this or you lose.
뭔가에 응답도 하고...
Something to do
with transponding.
그래! 응답... 응답사!
He's a transponster!
That's not even a word!
그건 단어도 아냐!
아는데, 뭐지? 뭐야?
I can get this! I can get this!
- 안돼!
- 아자!
-I call Monica's room.
-You can't just call Monica's room.
난 모니카의 방
엿장수 맘대로?
그럼, 간단한 규칙이잖아
먼저 찍는 사람이 임자야
Sure I can.
Standard shotgun rules.
I'm in sight of the room
and I called it.
Damn!
I feel like I'm coming down
with something.
몸이 안 좋아
- 정말?
- 그래
Guess the color of my tonsils.
I bet the apartment!
내 편도선은 무슨 색일까?
아파트 내기하자
I would never bet this place.
It's too nice.
왜 우리 아파트를 거나
이렇게 좋은데
얘들아
잘됐니?
Are they in there?
Yeah, I'm implanted.
그래, 이식했어
-How do you feel?
-Well, freaked.
기분이 어때?
그냥, 돌겠다
확률이 너무 희박해
It turns out the odds
are really sucky.
And this is
Frank and Alice's only shot.
게다가 동생부부한테
마지막 기회인데
They are literally putting
all their eggs in my basket.
그 집 계란을 몽땅
내 바구니에 넣었잖니
But I bet it works.
꼭 성공할 거야
Really? How much?
진짜? 얼마 걸래
I'm going to take
a pregnancy test now.
당장 임신테스트 해봐야겠어
Wow! You can tell this soon?
벌써 알 수 있대?
The doctor says it takes a few days.
의사는 며칠 걸린다고 했지만
내 몸은 서양의학보다
늘 한발 앞서나가거든
But my body's always been a little
faster than Western medicine.
I can't believe you guys think
you're moving in here.
세상에, 너희들 진짜로
이사 오는 건 아니겠지?
왜 아니겠어?
Well, believe it, baby!
-Well, I'm not moving.
-What?
난 못 나가
뭐?
바보 같은 내기였어
장난이었잖아
No. It was a stupid bet.
We were just playing a game.
You can't ignore the bet.
It's a bet!
내기는 엄연히 내기야
지면 뺏기는 내기라고
Bet on a bet
and if you lose, you lose the bet.
레이첼, 비워주자
We have to move.
We would have made them
get rid of the birds.
우리도 닭이랑 오리를
정말 없애려고 했잖아
아니...
누군 좋아서 이러니?
그래도 넌 나아
I hate this as much as you,
but if it makes you feel better...
...this is all your fault.
다 네 잘못이니까
What?
뭐?
Chanandler Bong!
We steal that TV Guide every week!
채낸들러 봉!
우리가 매주 훔쳐본 거잖아
I knew it!
그럴 줄 알았어!
I don't care.
I'm not going anywhere.
어쨌든 난 못 나가
Cool! Girl roommate.
좋지, 여자 룸메이트라
Well?
어때?
Nope, not knocked up yet.
아직 성사가 안됐어
It's only been a couple hours.
몇 시간 안됐잖아
느긋하게 생각해
Meanwhile, I'll do
whatever I can to help this.
맞아, 그 동안에
뭐든 해봐야겠다
I'm just going to, you know,
lie in your chair, okay?
나 여기 좀 누워있을게
Good. I'm going
to let gravity do its job.
됐다, 그렇지
중력의 힘을 빌어야지
I won't get in the way.
난 괜찮아
It'll be just like that time I tried to
count all the bumps on your ceiling.
전에 천장 무늬 보며
놀 때도 이랬잖니
You know, Pheebs, if you sit there long
enough, you'll be sitting in our apartment.
여긴 우리 집이라는
사실만 알아두세요
I can't believe this.
돌아가시겠네
Oh, Rach, FYl: Your new apartment
hasn't had hot water since Christmas.
참고로 말하는데 너희 새 아파트
성탄절 이후로 온수가 안 나온대
Can you give me a hand?
레이첼, 같이 좀 들자
싫어! 그거 당장 내려놔!
우린 아무 데도 안 가!
Put that box down!
We are not going anywhere!
This is my apartment and I like it!
여긴 내 아파트고
난 여기가 좋아
This is a girl's apartment!
여긴 여자들 아파트야
That is a boy's apartment!
It's dirty and it smells!
저긴 사내놈들 아파트고
더럽고 냄새나는 집!
이 집은 얼마나 예쁘니!
This is pretty!
It's so pretty!
And look, it's purple!
이걸 봐, 보라색이야!
너, 손 안 떠는 아가씨
I tell you, you with your
steady hand, I am not moving.
난 절대 못 나가
내 손도 안 떨리잖아
And now I have got the steady hand.
Okay, okay.
그래, 알았어
-I'll take care of it.
-That's right.
나한테 맡겨
그래! 네 손이
시키는 대로 해!
You do what the hand says!
-How'd it go?
-I lost our mattresses.
어떻게 됐어?
매트리스도 뺏겼다
앙증맞은 태아야
아홉 달 후에 만나자
Are you in there, little fetus?
In nine months will you come greet us?
아디다스를 사줄게
I will buy you some Adidas
- 안녕하세요?
- 어서 와요
피비
약국에 들러서
선물 좀 사왔어요
We were just at the drugstore
so we got you a little present.
워우, 피가 내려온다
That's where all my blood was.
It's a lollipop
and a home pregnancy test.
막대사탕이랑
임신진단기구야
얘, 헷갈리지 마라
막대사탕 버린다
Don't mix those up.
You could really ruin that lollipop.
지금 테스트해볼래요?
문제는 딱 한 개인데
You feel like taking a test?
There's only one question.
All right. I will.
좋아요, 해볼게요
Remember that
it's still really early.
하지만 아직 이르다는 건 알죠?
혹시 아니라고 나와도
실패했단 뜻은 아니에요
If it says I'm not pregnant, that
doesn't mean I won't get pregnant.
나도 좀 부담스러우니까
너무 큰 기대는 갖지 말아요
Just so I don't go completely nuts...
...try not to put
all your hopes on this.
- 알았어요
- 그럼
Great.
고마워요
You are mean boys
who are just being mean!
너희들 알고 보니까
정말 치사한 인간들이다
왜 우리한테 이래
누가 판돈 올리랬어?
Don't get mad! No one
forced you to raise the stakes.
무슨 소리, 판돈을
올린 건 모니카야
That is not true!
She forced me!
그 문제만 맞혔으면
우리가 왜 쫓겨나니
You got the question wrong.
거지같은 문제였어
It was a stupid, unfair question!
문제 탓하지 마
Don't blame the questions!
Stop yelling in our apartment!
You are ruining moving day for us.
왜 남의 집에서 떠들어
이삿날 기분 잡치게
- 여기가 왜 너희 집이야
- 그럼 누구 집이냐...
-Stop calling it your apartment!
-lt is!
You're going to have a baby.
They're going to have a baby!
아이를 가졌어
성공이야!
My sister's going to have my baby!
우리 누나가 내 아이를 가졌다!
Okay, but this can't
be good for the baby.
이럼 아기한테 안 좋아
I can't find garbage bags.
쓰레기봉투 없니?
여기 어디 있던데
I think I saw some in here.
What is it?
저게 뭐지?
I don't know. But maybe if we keep
that drawer shut, it'll die.
뭔지는 모르겠지만
죽을 때까지 기다리자
I can't believe we're living here!
우리 신세가 어쩌다 이렇게 됐니
What is it?
왜 그래!
저 옷장 크기 봤냐?
Did you see the size of the closets?
I can't believe we live here!
우리 신세가 어쩌다 이렇게 폈니